[
  {
    "answer": 2,
    "question": "Who is responsible for national economic management? ",
    "options": [
      "State and territory governments",
      "The Council of Australian local government",
      "The Australian Federal government"
    ],
    "id": 1
  },
  {
    "answer": 0,
    "question": "Which statement about Australia\u2019s democracy system is correct? ",
    "options": [
      "Citizens freely choose representatives to given the country and make laws on their behalf",
      "Citizens propose and make laws directly through parliament",
      "Selected Citizens advise, propose and change laws with government officials"
    ],
    "id": 2
  },
  {
    "answer": 2,
    "question": "What are the three colours of the Australian Aboriginal Flag?",
    "options": ["Black, Red, Green", "Red, Black, White", "Black, Red, Yellow"],
    "id": 3
  },
  {
    "answer": 0,
    "question": "\u201cIt identifies the authority and property of the Commonwealth of Australia\u201d - What is this sentence referring to?",
    "options": [
      "The Commonwealth Coat of Arms",
      "The Coat of Australia",
      "The Federation of Australia"
    ],
    "id": 4
  },
  {
    "answer": 1,
    "question": "How do you express your democratic beliefs as an Australian citizen?",
    "options": [
      "By going to church.",
      "By living peacefully, respecting all",
      "By having a stable job."
    ],
    "id": 5
  },
  {
    "answer": 1,
    "question": "During which period of time did migration levels rise and fall?",
    "options": [
      "First half of the 19th century",
      "First half of the 20th century",
      "Last half of the 20th century"
    ],
    "id": 6
  },
  {
    "answer": 2,
    "question": "Who was Captain Arthur Phillip?",
    "options": [
      "First Premier of Queensland",
      "First Governor General of Australia",
      "The commander of first fleet in Australia"
    ],
    "id": 7
  },
  {
    "answer": 1,
    "question": "Why is the Floral Emblem famous in Australia?",
    "options": [
      "It is Australian National Flag",
      "It is Australia\u2019s National Flower",
      "It is Australian National Fruit"
    ],
    "id": 8
  },
  {
    "answer": 0,
    "question": "The power and authority to make and change the laws in Australia is called: ",
    "options": ["Legislative Power", "Executive Power", "Judicial Power"],
    "id": 9
  },
  {
    "answer": 2,
    "question": "On which occasion or special events can we sing Australia\u2019s national anthem? ",
    "options": [
      "At Australian Citizenship Ceremonies",
      "Major Sporting Events",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "id": 10
  }
]